myactv.net 2018-07-27

# Antietam Broadband - High Speed Cable Internet ISP - Hagerstown / Washington County, MD

We take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. Antietam Broadband ("AB") is the owner of AntietamBroadband.net and retains all ownership rights to the information collected at this site. However, in the event that we are involved in a sale of a substantial portion of our business assets, customer information may be among the transferred assets.

##### What this Privacy Policy Covers

The purpose of AntietamBroadband.net's Privacy Policy is to inform you of AB's practices with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information, and aggregate information that is anonymous (such as your IP address). Personally identifiable information is information that allows us to contact you (name, home address, home and work telephone numbers, e-mail address, interests, age, gender and income). This policy supplements our Acceptable Use Policy ("AUP"), which we also urge you to read. By using our website and the Service, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy and by our AUP. 

This policy does not apply to practices of companies that AB does not own or control or to people that AB does not employ or manage. 

##### The Cable Privacy Act

In addition, as an AB cable customer, you are entitled under federal law to a statement about our collection and use of certain information that we learn about you. That information is required to be provided in a separate written statement and is therefore attached to this Privacy Policy as Annex A.

##### Information Collection and Use

We collect personally identifiable information when you when you register for the Service, take surveys, and when you enter promotions, sweepstakes or contest. We may receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 

We collect the following types of personally identifiable information regarding our subscribers: name; home address; home and work telephone numbers; e-mail addresses; interests; age; gender; billing and credit card information; payment and credit records; social security or drivers license number; levels of service subscribed to; software/hardware used; web site addresses.

Web servers serving our web site may automatically track information about which pages you visit on our server, as well as your IP address or domain name. This information may be used for our internal web site business purposes, for example, to tailor our web site content or to assess the amount of traffic to our web site. We may also provide this information on an aggregated, anonymous basis to our advertisers.

We use information for the following general purposes: to customize advertising and content and contact you about specials and new products. 

##### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. 

From time to time we may share your personally identifiable information with other businesses, including our marketing partners and advertisers or companies who work on behalf of AB to provide the product or service that you requested. If you object to such use of information you have submitted, you will have the opportunity to indicate your objection when entering such information or you may contact: webmaster@myactv.net.

We will provide your personally identifiable information (i) to comply with the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, the Digital Millennium Copyright Act or any other law; (ii) to enforce our AUP; (iii) to protect the integrity of AB's operations; (iv) to protect our customers; or (v) to prevent a crime. You expressly grant AB permission to disclose personal information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, civil investigative demands or other legal process.

##### IP addresses and Log Files

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our website, analyze trends, track users' webpage movements on our servers, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may also log SMTP and POP information.

##### Cookies 

From time to time, we may place a "cookie" on your computer. A cookie is a file written to your computer's hard drive that records certain technical information about your Internet usage, such as your IP address, browser type, or domain name. Also, if you submit personal information to our web site (such as your name, address, interests or preferences), we may use cookies to keep track of such information so that you will not need to reenter this information during subsequent visits. Cookies help us to customize delivery of our web site content and advertisements. You may set your Internet browser preferences to notify you when you receive a cookie or to decline acceptance of cookies. 

##### Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

You have the ability to edit some account information from password protected web-based administration forms. This account information includes the password used to access the administrative forms, name, title, address, telephone numbers, contact e-mail address and URL. 

##### Security

Your information is protected in a variety of ways, including firewall rule sets, unique user name and password combinations, and Intrusion Detection software.

However, we cannot and do not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You transmit information to us at your own risk.

##### Banner Advertising and Links to Other Sites

You should be aware that when you are on the web site you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. We may provide links to other sites and banner advertisements. If you click on a banner advertisement or a link, the click takes you off the site. You may see links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use our logo as part of a co-branding agreement. We do not control the contents or links that appear on these sites. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. In addition, these sites or services, including their contents and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and terms and conditions of use, or no policies at all. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information.

##### Third Parties

Occasionally we may enter into relationships with other companies to provide additional features at this site. We may become business partners with other companies, other companies may become sponsors, or we may "co-brand" our site with others. Any personal information you provide when signing up at one of these co-branded pages may be shared with our third party partner.

##### Children's Privacy Policy

You must be 18 or older to sign up for an account with AB. We do not knowingly collect information about children. For parents who are subscribers to the Service, we recommend that you participate in your child's experience on the Internet.

##### Changes to this Privacy Policy

AB reserves the right to revise this policy, or any part thereof, or impose new conditions, without advance notice. We will post revision to this policy on this site. Use of the Service following such revisions or additions constitutes your acceptance of the revised policy. Accordingly, we urge you to frequently review this Privacy Policy, and, if you do not agree to the terms of this or any revised policy, please exit the site immediately.

##### Miscellaneous

Questions regarding the above policy should be directed to [webmaster@myactv.net](mailto:webmaster@myactv.net) for clarification.

Last updated: April 11, 2002

All contents of AntietamBroadband.net are: copyright 2017 Antietam Broadband, Inc., 1000 Willow Circle, Hagerstown, Maryland 21740 U.S.A. All rights reserved.
